Farewell, Earth
The ship that is departing is
The Space Battleship
Yamato
It departs now to Iscandar,
at the end of the cosmos,
bearing its fate.
"We will come back, no matter what it takes"
Answer with a smile to the waving people
Going far from the Galaxy towards Iscandar
A faint gleam of hope
The Space Battleship Yamato
Garmillas
Beloved citizens of the Great Garmillas Empire,
I know the crown of glory on my head is a gift made possible by your loyalty
to the nation and to this planet, to Great Garmillas.
I name you my friends,
and I am grateful to all of you for gathering here today.
Thank you.
Ghale Garmillon! Ghale Desler!
Ilun Phuzeron.
Miezela Celestella
Propaganda Minister
Lord Abelt Desler
Vice-Commander Redof Hyss
Velte Talan
Armaments Minister
Herm Zoellik
Inspector-General of the Central Army
Gul Ditz
Supreme Commander of Astrofleets
Ghader Talan
Vice-Chief of the General Staff
Heydom Gimleh
Imperial Guard Information Officer
Garemud Goer
Galactic Theater Commander
Episode 8
Wish Upon a Star
That girl was waving
A bright red scarf
Who do you think it was for?
Whoever it was
It doesn’t matter
Let each think it was for him
The hearts of men beginning a journey
Want a piece of romance
A bright red scarf